Espy, Watt; Papers apap301
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Documentation of Executions, 1730-2008; Undated; 2; 44.5 cubic ft.
  - State, 1730-2008; Undated; 2.1
    - New York, executions recorded in statewide records, Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - New York, unconfirmed and possible executions, 1839-1886; Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - North Carolina, A, 1825-1972; Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 19)
    - North Carolina, B, 1874-1996; Undated (Box 28 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 20)
    - North Carolina, B, 1822-1956; Undated (Box 29 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - North Carolina, B, 1847-1959; Undated (Box 29 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - North Carolina, C, 1830-1956; Undated (Box 29 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - North Carolina, C-D, 1851-1977; Undated (Box 29 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - North Carolina, D, 1773-1987; Undated (Box 29 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - North Carolina, E-F, 1831-1985; Undated (Box 29 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - North Carolina, F-G, 1888-1992; Undated (Box 29 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - North Carolina, G, 1818-1995; Undated (Box 29 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - North Carolina, H, 1849-1954; Undated (Box 29 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - North Carolina, H-I, 1880-1998; Undated (Box 29 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - North Carolina, J, 1856-1975; Undated (Box 29 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - North Carolina, J-K, 1830-1935; Undated (Box 29 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - North Carolina, L, 1868-1995; Undated (Box 29 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - North Carolina, M, 1921-1991; Undated (Box 29 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - North Carolina, M, 1829-1988; Undated (Box 29 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - North Carolina, M, 1827-1990; Undated (Box 29 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - North Carolina, O-P, 1858-1984; Undated (Box 29 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - North Carolina, P-R, 1878-1999; Undated (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - North Carolina, S, 1812-1853; Undated (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - North Carolina, S, 1810-1995; Undated (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - North Carolina, S, 1820-1984; Undated (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - North Carolina, T-W, 1810-1848; Undated (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - North Carolina, W, 1810-1987; Undated (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - North Carolina, W, 1854-1986; Undated (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - North Carolina, multiple executions, 1831-1964; Undated (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - North Carolina, executions recorded in city histories, 1983; 1984; 1988 (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - North Carolina, executions recorded in county histories, 1920-1985; Undated (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - North Carolina, executions recorded in statewide records, 1886-1901 (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - North Carolina, executions recorded in statewide records, 1907; 1937 (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - North Carolina, executions recorded in statewide records, 1928-1987; Undated (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - North Carolina, unconfirmed executions, 1827; 1831; 1858; 1937; Undated (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - North Dakota, 1885-1988; Undated (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Ohio, A-B, 1891-1982; Undated (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Ohio, B, 1872-1998; Undated (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Ohio, B-C, 1871-2001; Undated (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Ohio, C, 1844-1986; Undated (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 19)
    - Ohio, C-D, 1882-1974; Undated (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 20)
    - Ohio, D, 1864-1986; Undated (Box 30 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 21)
    - Ohio, D-E, 1876-1989; Undated (Box 31 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Ohio, E-F, 1889-1969; Undated (Box 31 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Ohio, F-G, 1897-1982; Undated (Box 31 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Ohio, G-H, 1874-1984; Undated (Box 31 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Ohio, H, 1927-1974 (Box 31 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Ohio, H, 1892-1982; Undated (Box 31 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Ohio, H-J, 1871-1969; Undated (Box 31 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Ohio, J-L, 1884-1974; Undated (Box 31 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Ohio, L-M, 1878-1984; Undated (Box 31 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Ohio, M, 1876-1974; Undated (Box 31 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Ohio, M-P, 1864-1975; Undated (Box 31 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Ohio, P, 1890-1952; Undated (Box 31 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Ohio, P-R, 1922-1997; Undated (Box 31 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Ohio, R, 1921-1990; Undated (Box 31 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Ohio, R-S, 1870-1978; Undated (Box 31 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Ohio, S, 1930-1997; Undated (Box 31 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Ohio, S-T, 1888-1996; Undated (Box 31 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Ohio, T, 1882-1984; Undated (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Ohio, T-V, 1922-1976; Undated (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Ohio, W, 1878-1987; Undated (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Ohio, W, Y, 1891-1991; Undated (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Ohio, multiple executions, 1867-1991; Undated (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Ohio, executions recorded in city and county histories, 1878-1985; Undated (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Ohio, executions recorded in statewide records, 1965-1991; Undated (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Oklahoma, B-C, 1891-1997; Undated (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Oklahoma, C, 1939-1992 (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Oklahoma, D, F, 1933-1998; Undated (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Oklahoma, F-H, 1927-1995; Undated (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Oklahoma, H-K, 1908-1996; Undated (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Oklahoma, L-O, 1933-1998; Undated (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Oklahoma, O-P, 1940-1992; Undated (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Oklahoma, Q-R, 1932-1985; Undated (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Oklahoma, R-S, 1922-1999; Undated (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Oklahoma, S-T, W, 1940-1995; Undated (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Oklahoma, W, 1940-1980 (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Oklahoma, executions recorded in statewide records, 1979; Undated (Box 32 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 19)
    - Oregon, A-C, 1902-1996; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Oregon, C-E, 1902-1979; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Oregon, F, H, 1894-1998; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Oregon, H, J-K, 1911-1975; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Oregon, L, 1878-1985; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Oregon, L-M, 1887-1997; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Oregon, N-S, 1877-1977; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Oregon, S-T, W, 1908-1991; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Oregon, W, Z, 1977-1996; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Oregon, unidentified and multiple exec., 1873-1977; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Oregon, executions recorded in county and statewide records, 1951; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Pennsylvania, A-B, 1858-1984; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Pennsylvania, B, 1878-1988; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Pennsylvania, B-C, 1894-1978; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania, C, 1799-1987; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Pennsylvania, D, 1923-1977; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Pennsylvania, D, 1867-1987; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Pennsylvania, D-E, 1879-1990; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Pennsylvania, E, 1920-1989; Undated (Box 33 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 19)
    - Pennsylvania, E-F, 1866-1975; Undated (Box 34 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania, F-G, 1852-1987; Undated (Box 34 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania, G-H, 1901-1986; Undated (Box 34 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania, H, 1894-1997; Undated (Box 34 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania, H-J, 1875-1985; Undated (Box 34 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania, J-K, 1878-1987; Undated (Box 34 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania, K-M, 1822-1987; Undated (Box 34 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania, M, 1808-1959; Undated (Box 34 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania, M, 1932-1987; Undated (Box 34 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania, M, 1832-1995; Undated (Box 34 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania, P, 1866-1995; Undated (Box 34 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Pennsylvania, P, 1938-1957; Undated (Box 34 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Pennsylvania, P-R, 1909-1975; Undated (Box 34 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Pennsylvania, R-S, 1878-1949; Undated (Box 34 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania, S, 1853-1995; Undated (Box 34 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Pennsylvania, S-T, 1915-1956; Undated (Box 34 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Pennsylvania, T-U, 1824-1975; Undated (Box 34 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Pennsylvania, V-W, 1908-1976; Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania, Z, 1985-1995 (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania and Minnesota newspaper accounts of executions, 1862; 1904; Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania, unidentified and multiple executions, 1877-1970; Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania, executions recorded in city, county and statewide records, 1866-1992; Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Rhode Island, A-M, 1737-1988; Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Rhode Island, P-W, 1832-1988; Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Rhode Island, unidentified and multiple executions, Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Rhode Island, executions recorded in statewide records, 1974-1988 (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - South Carolina, A-B, 1899-1996; Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - South Carolina, B, 1875-1982; Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - South Carolina, B-D, 1800-1984; Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - South Carolina, D-F, 1820-1997; Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - South Carolina, G, 1908-1991; Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - South Carolina, H, J, 1809-1988; Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - South Carolina, J-M, 1791-1996; Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - South Carolina, M-P, R, 1846-1996; Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - South Carolina, R-S, 1909-1998; Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - South Carolina, S-T, 1876-1998; Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - South Carolina, T, V-W, Y, 1785-1998; Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 19)
    - South Carolina, unidentified executions, Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 20)
    - South Carolina, multiple executions, 1893-1982; Undated (Box 35 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 21)
    - South Carolina, multiple executions, 1877-1987; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - South Carolina, executions recorded in city and county histories, 1892-1987; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - South Carolina, executions recorded in statewide records, 1963-1981; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - South Carolina, unconfirmed executions, 1793-1832; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - South Dakota, 1902-1992; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Tennessee, A-B, 1826-1981; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Tennessee, B-C, 1843-2000; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Tennessee, D-H, 1879-1997; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Tennessee, H, 1843-1964; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Tennessee, J-K, 1801-1991; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Tennessee, L-N, 1867-1983; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Tennessee, O-S, 1819-1992; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Tennessee, T-Y, 1883-1960; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Tennessee, multiple executions, 1890-1939; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Tennessee, executions recorded in city and county histories, 1946-1983; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Tennessee, executions recorded in statewide records, 1886-1982; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Texas, A, 1879-1995; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Texas, A-B, 1907-1997; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Texas, B, 1883-1997; Undated (Box 36 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 19)
    - Texas, B, 1873-2002; Undated (Box 37 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Texas, B, 1861-1998; Undated (Box 37 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Texas, B, 1878-1997; Undated (Box 37 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Texas, B, 1879-1997; Undated (Box 37 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Texas, B, 1918-1963; Undated (Box 37 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Texas, B-C, 1898-1991; Undated (Box 37 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Texas, C, 1880-1997; Undated (Box 37 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Texas, C, 1879-1997; Undated (Box 37 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Texas, C-D, 1874-1994; Undated (Box 37 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Texas, D, 1884-1999; Undated (Box 37 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Texas, D-E, 1923-1999; Undated (Box 37 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Texas, E, 1955-1992; Undated (Box 37 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Texas, F, 1891-1999; Undated (Box 37 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Texas, G, 1879-1997; Undated (Box 37 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Texas, G, 1885-1974; Undated (Box 37 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Texas, G, 1922-2000; Undated (Box 37 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Texas, G-H, 1878-1994; Undated (Box 38 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Texas, H, 1900-1997; Undated (Box 38 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Texas, H, 1871-1995; Undated (Box 38 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Texas, H, 1938-1998; Undated (Box 38 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Texas, H, 1892-1973; Undated (Box 38 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Texas, H, J, 1915-2000; Undated (Box 38 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Texas, J, 1948-1997; Undated (Box 38 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Texas, J, 1838-1995; Undated (Box 38 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Texas, J-K, 1898-1993; Undated (Box 38 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Texas, K-L, 1901-1997; Undated (Box 38 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Texas, L, 1877-1997; Undated (Box 38 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Texas, L-M, 1862-1998; Undated (Box 38 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Texas, M, 1896-1995; Undated (Box 38 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Texas, M, 1889-1995; Undated (Box 38 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Texas, M, 1869-1998; Undated (Box 38 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Texas, M, 1934-1997; Undated (Box 38 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Texas, M, 1898-1987; Undated (Box 39 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Texas, M-O, 1880-1998; Undated (Box 39 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Texas, O-P, 1878-1900; Undated (Box 39 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Texas, P, 1926-1993; Undated (Box 39 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Texas, P-R, 1901-1998; Undated (Box 39 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Texas, R, 1885-1997; Undated (Box 39 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Texas, R, 1926-1998; Undated (Box 39 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Texas, R-S, 1913-1995; Undated (Box 39 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Texas, S, 1893-1997; Undated (Box 39 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Texas, S, 1891-1991; Undated (Box 39 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Texas, S, 1878-1997; Undated (Box 39 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Texas, S-T, 1882-1998; Undated (Box 39 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Texas, T-V, 1879-1998; Undated (Box 39 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Texas, V-W, 1882-1995; Undated (Box 39 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Texas, W, 1886-1997; Undated (Box 39 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Texas, W, 1947-1993; Undated (Box 39 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Texas, W, 1908-1995; Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Texas, W-Y, 1886-1997; Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Texas, multiple executions, 1924; 1968; 1984 (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Texas, executions recorded in city histories, 1968-1985; Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Texas, executions recorded in county histories, 1882-1988; Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Texas, executions recorded in county histories, 1936-1995; Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Texas, executions recorded in county histories, 1949-1982; Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Texas, executions recorded in statewide records, 1948-1998; Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Texas, unconfirmed and possible executions, 1898-1995; Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Utah, A-C, 1922-1996 (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Utah, C-F, 1888-1984; Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Utah, G-F, 1887-1994; Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Utah, K-M, 1869-1997; Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Utah, N-W, 1879-1999; Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Utah, executions recorded in statewide records, 1951-1975; Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Vermont, A-M, 1839-1985; Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Vermont, M-W, 1867-1975; Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 17)
    - Vermont, executions recorded in statewide records, Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 18)
    - Virginia, A, 1795-1981; Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 19)
    - Virginia, A-B, 1805-1995; Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 20)
    - Virginia, B, 1791-1997; Undated (Box 40 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 21)
    - Virginia, B, 1922-1990; Undated (Box 41 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Virginia, B-C, 1815-1997; Undated (Box 41 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Virginia, C, 1787-1991; Undated (Box 41 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Virginia, C, 1887-1992; Undated (Box 41 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Virginia, C, 1821-1996; Undated (Box 41 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Virginia, D-E, 1765-1998; Undated (Box 41 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Virginia, E-F, 1806-1992; Undated (Box 41 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Virginia, F-G, 1796-1999; Undated (Box 41 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)
    - Virginia, G-H, 1900-1997; Undated (Box 41 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 9)
    - Virginia, H, 1822-1996; Undated (Box 41 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 10)
    - Virginia, I-J, 1818-1992; Undated (Box 41 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 11)
    - Virginia, J-L, 1883-1991; Undated (Box 41 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 12)
    - Virginia, L-M, 1896-1985; Undated (Box 41 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 13)
    - Virginia, M, 1808-1997; Undated (Box 41 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 14)
    - Virginia, N-P, 1772-1999; Undated (Box 41 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 15)
    - Virginia, P, R, 1813-1993; Undated (Box 41 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 16)
    - Virginia, R-S, 1801-1997; Undated (Box 42 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 1)
    - Virginia, S, 1902-1994 (Box 42 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 2)
    - Virginia, S-T, 1777-1998; Undated (Box 42 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 3)
    - Virginia, T,V-W, 1805-1997; Undated (Box 42 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 4)
    - Virginia, W, 1807-1993; Undated (Box 42 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 5)
    - Virginia, W, Y, 1787-1999; Undated (Box 42 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 6)
    - Virginia, unidentified executions, 1860-1990; Undated (Box 42 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 7)
    - Virginia, multiple executions, 1778-1989; Undated (Box 42 (2-Documentation of Executions), Folder 8)